oneblockdown.it 2017-05-01

# Privacy policy | One Block Down Online Store

**Your Privacy**  
ONE BLOCK DOWN Limited ("ONE BLOCK DOWN") is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The ONE BLOCK DOWN team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

**Your Consent**  
We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission, but we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the ONE BLOCK DOWN website.

**Communication & Marketing**  
If you have made a purchase from our store we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mai. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you become a member of ONE BLOCK DOWN. All ONE BLOCK DOWN members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by visiting 'Your Details' in 'Your Account' on the ONE BLOCK DOWN website. You can access 'Your Account' once you register and login. Or click on the "unsubscribe" link in any email communications which we might send you.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website and it will recognise your device on future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your preferences and chosen items, assisting you to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you. These "cookies" can be divided into 4 types each of which is outlined below.

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**  
These cookies are essential in order to enable the site to provide services you have asked for such as remembering your shopping bag items.

**Performance Cookies**  
This type collect anonymous information on how people use the site and the data is merged with other users to enable us to improve how the site operates. For example we utilise Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

**Functionality Cookies**  
These remember choices you make such as language, search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate with your selections and make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information is also merged with other users on an anonymous basis to enable us to improve how the site operates. For example our Saved Items feature utilises a cookie to remember the products which you have expressed a wish to save whilst browsing our website.

**Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies**  
These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. 

**Site Statistics**  
We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. ONE BLOCK DOWN uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us here.

**Protecting your security**  
We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

**Disclosures of your information**  
We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:  
in the event that ONE BLOCK DOWN sells or buys any business or assets;  
if ONE BLOCK DOWN or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ONE BLOCK DOWN, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third party sites**  
Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Checking your Details**  
If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to ONE BLOCK DOWN you may do so by contacting us via the e-mail address or address given below. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

**Contacting us**  
ONE BLOCK DOWN.com (ONE BLOCK DOWN) Limited (at the address below) is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

You have the right to access the information which ONE BLOCK DOWN holds about you and your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. You may lodge an access request for free, but depending upon the personal information you request, we may impose a charge to recover our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. We will notify you of any such change upon receiving your access request, and confirm whether you wish to proceed and pay such charge.

We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact a customer service member of the ONE BLOCK DOWN team, who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.

You can either contact customer care  
Or, write to us at:

contact@oneblockdown.it
